Guide to the Frank M. Ingalls Photograph Collection ca. 1901-1930 PR 28
New-York Historical Society
Frank M. Ingalls photograph collection
ca. 1901-1930 (bulk 1904-1910)
New-York Historical Society
PR 28
6.09 Linear feet (14 boxes)
The Frank M. Ingalls Collection includes photographs taken around lower Manhattan and Queens. The majority of the views are of skyscraper and building construction and street scenes. The Frank M. Ingalls Collection is digitized and available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Biographical Note
Frank Munroe Ingalls, a self-taught photographer active in New York City from 1901-1935, was born in Nashua, New Hampshire, on June 12, 1862, to Lyman Ingalls and Mary Ellen Fairbanks Ingalls. He worked in Nashua as a clerk and then a printer at George Bagley & Co., a stationery store and printing shop. He married Bertha Frazier in 1882, and their daughter Clara (known as Claire) was born in 1883. During the mid-1890s, Ingalls worked as a draftsman in the Engineer's Office of the City of Nashua; about this time, he became interested in photography. In 1899, he took over ownership of the former Powers photography studio at 63 Main Street in Nashua.
Ingalls moved his family to New York City in 1901, and set about documenting the cultural landscape of his new home almost immediately. In a series of illustrated articles published between 1906 and 1911 in the American Annual of Photography, Ingalls wrote, "…the skyline of lower Manhattan is a very interesting subject, as it is constantly changing from year to year." He also noted that he always carried a small camera with him, even when it rained, to be sure he never missed an unexpected opportunity. A member of the Camera Club of the 23rd St. YMCA, he published designs for a camera club's rooms based on his own club experience; his articles offered advice on the best equipment and sites for photographing New York City. The 1920 census shows that Ingalls lived in Queens with his daughter; it lists his occupation as "lantern slide creator."
In 1935, Ingalls returned to Nashua and set up a photography studio in his home on Concord Street. He became active at the Nashua Historical Society, preserving old photographs and maps of Nashua. He continued to document Nashua through his photography. Ingalls moved to Fitchburg, Massachusetts, in late 1942, and the next year donated his collection of approximately 850 images of New York City to the New-York Historical Society. Some time after, Ingalls moved to Florida, where he lived with his daughter. He died in Clermont, Florida, in February 1956; he is buried at the Woodlawn Cemetery in Nashua, NH.
Access
The collection is open to qualified researchers. Portions of the collection that have been photocopied or microfilmed will be brought to the researcher in that format; microfilm can be made available through Interlibrary Loan.
Separated Materials
The majority of the film negatives are cellulose nitrate, and have been physically removed from the rest of the collection. If you need to consult these negatives, please contact a staff member for assistance.
Provenance
Gift of Frank M. Ingalls, January 28, 1943, and May 10, 1945.
Restrictions
Access Restrictions Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. See guidelines in Print Room for details.
Use Restrictions Permission to reproduce any Print Room holdings through publication must be obtained from:
Rights and Reproductions The New-York Historical Society 170 Central Park West New York, NY 10024 Phone: (212) 873-3400 ext. 282 Fax: (212) 579-8794
Arrangement
The collection is divided into series based on format: Prints and Negatives.
Scope and Content Note
The Frank M. Ingalls Photograph Collection spans the period from ca. 1901-1930 and is comprised of 802 images of New York City and its immediate environs. The collection is divided into series based on format: Prints and Negatives. Modern prints made from vintage negatives are filed at the end of the collection.
The photographs document an era in which the cityscape was rapidly being transformed by an upswing in the cycle of demolition and construction that has characterized so much of the history of New York City. The changing skyline of Manhattan, including panoramic views of the city and skyscrapers under construction, are common subjects. The construction of the Singer Building and the Metropolitan Life Building are particularly well documented. Other well-represented structures include bridges, statues, and monuments. Also present in great numbers are images of different types of ships and boats in the waters around Manhattan, such as steamships, yachts, tugboats, ferryboats, and excursion boats.
Various facets of Manhattan life are depicted in Ingalls' street scenes: a push cart market; snow removers; horse carts; newsboys; a pretzel vendor; a stilt-walker advertising various establishments; parades; flag-draped buildings; automobiles; and fireworks displays. In particular, Ingalls seemed to be interested in the juxtaposition of horse-drawn vehicles with mechanical vehicles. Many sets of views are the same basic view, one showing a horse-drawn bus, for example, and the next with an automotive bus. Scenes of Central Park and Coney Island are also prominent. The collection holds a few portraits, including two self-portraits of the photographer. A few night views show lights at Coney Island, and also the new Times Building in Times Square.
Within each series, images are arranged numerically according to Ingalls' own numbering system. Each image is captioned and some are dated; however, the majority of images are undated. Approximate dates have been assigned where possible by using activities documented in the image. A complete listing of image numbers, dates, and captions, which were transcribed from Ingalls' original negative enclosures, appears after the box listing. When there are multiple images of a given subject taken at the same time, they are denoted by consecutive letters following a number. The unnumbered images all seem to date from Ingalls' 1945 donation of material. They include views of boats and ships, the interior of the B. Altman Department Store at 34th Street and Fifth Avenue, and a set of views of Queens towns.
A negative exists for most of the 802 images; there is also an existing original print for the majority of the negatives. The collection includes: 250 glass plate negatives in 5 x 7-inch or smaller format; 517 film negatives, ranging in size from 2 x 3 inches to 3 x 7 inches (including 181 stereograph negatives); and 570 prints, ranging in size from 2 x 3 inches to 5 x 7 inches. There are 228 negatives that do not have original prints; these are indicated in the image list with an asterisk next to their numbers. 229 prints do not have corresponding negatives.
Series I. Prints consists of 570 prints, arranged numerically by Ingalls' image numbers. A list of numbers and titles follows the box listing. Unnumbered prints, mainly unidentified views of Queens, are filed after the numbered photographs.
Series II. Negatives consists of 767 negatives, both film and glass. They are arranged in two subseries by medium, then filed numerically by Ingalls' image numbers. The majority of the film negatives are cellulose nitrate, and have been physically removed from the rest of the collection. If you need to consult these negatives, please contact a staff member for assistance.
- Series I. Photographic prints
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Digital copies of prints are available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
  - Subseries I.1: Individually cataloged prints (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1, Box-folder 1)
    - 1b, Aquarium, Battery Park, snow (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1c, Aquarium, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1d, Aquarium, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 3a, Whitehall Building, 17 Battery Place, before addition, snow (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 3b, Whitehall Building, 17 Battery Place, addition of 1-14 West Street under construction (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 3c, Whitehall Building, 17 Battery Place, addition of 1-14 West Street under construction (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 3d, Whitehall Building, 17 Battery Place, after addition of 1-14 West Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 3e, Whitehall Building, 17 Battery Place, after addition of 1-14 West Street, taken from water (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 4a, Washington Building, 1 Broadway, Battery Park, 1925 or later (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 4b, Washington Building, 1 Broadway, under construction, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 5a, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 5b, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 5c, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 5d, Maritime Building, 8-10 Bridge Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6a, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6b, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6c, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6d, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway, under construction (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6e, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6f, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6g, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 6h, New York Produce Exchange Bank building, 10-12 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 7a, 10-12 Broadway, addition to Standard Oil Building, under construction, 1923 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 7b, 10-12 Broadway, addition to Standard Oil Building, 1923 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 8a, Washington Building, 1 Broadway, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 8b, Washington Building, 1 Broadway, Battery Park, delivery wagon (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 9, West Street Building, 90 West Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 10a Consolidated Stock Exchange, southeast corner of Beaver and Broad Streets (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 10b Consolidated Stock Exchange, southeast corner of Beaver and Broad Streets (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 10c, Consolidated Stock Exchange, southeast corner of Beaver and Broad Streets (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 11a, 29 Broadway, 61 Broadway in background, 1908 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 11b, 29 Broadway, 61 Broadway in background, 1908 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 12, Hazeltine's Dining Rooms, 41 Broad Street, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 15, New York Stock Exchange (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 19a, Conte Restaurant, 434 Lafayette Street, Lafayette Terrace Buildings, 1907 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 20, Siegel Cooper Department Store, Sixth Avenue and 18th Street, 1907 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 23, Appelate Court building, 27 Madison Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 24a, New York Times Building, Broadway and 42nd Street, night view, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 24b, New York Times Building, Broadway and 42nd Street, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 26, YMCA, 23rd Street and Seventh Avenue, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27a, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27b, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street, and Maritime building (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27c, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27d, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27e, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27f, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27g, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1a, Aquarium, Battery Park, snow (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27h, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27l, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27j, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street, and Maritime building (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 29, YMCA, 57th Street west of Eighth Avenue, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 27k, US Custom House, State Street and Whitehall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 28, YMCA, frame-type building (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 30, New York Central Railroad Freight Yard, West 60th Street and Hudson River (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 31, Schwab Mansion, Riverside Drive between 73rd Street and 74th Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 33, American Museum of Natural History, West 77th Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 34, Claremont Inn and Grant's Tomb, Riverside Drive (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 37a, Low Library, Columbia University, ball on steps (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 38, Hotel Oakland (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 40, Custom House, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 43, Battery Park, Aquarium in distance, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 44, Beekman Street looking west (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 45a, Continental Bank and Trust Company under construction, 30 Broad Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 46, Broad Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 48, Broadway looking north from Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 49b, Broadway and Morris Street, northwest corner, Sapolio sign (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 49a, Broadway and Morris Street, northwest corner, Sapolio sign (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 50a, 163-169 West 23rd Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 50b, 163-167 West 23rd Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - 51, 23rd Street near Sixth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 52, Fourth Avenue near 17th Street looking north (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 53a, Chambers Street, horse-drawn cart overturned (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 53b, Chambers Street, horse-drawn cart overturned (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 53c, Chambers Street, horse-drawn streetcar (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 54, City Hall (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55a, Central Park, family strolling, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55b, Central Park, horse-drawn cart, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55c, Central Park, automobile on road, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55d, Central Park, boaters, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55e, Central Park, children on steps, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55f, Central Park, autombile on road, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55g, Central Park, two horses and riders, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 55h, Central Park, picnickers, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 56a, Coney Island, bathers, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 56b, Coney Island, Dreamland at night, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 56c, Coney Island, bathers, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 56d, Coney Island, Balmer's Bath House, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 58, 235-237 28th Street at Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 60, 255 Fifth Avenue, new motor bus (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 61, Fifth Avenue, waste paper collectors (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 62, 25th Street and Fifth Avenue, Madison Square Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 63, Bronze traffic towers on Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 64, Fifth Avenue at 46th Street looking north, automobile congestion, 1928 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 65, Fifth Avenue at 59th Street looking west over Central Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 66, Fifth Avenue around 86th Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 68, Governor's Island (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 69, Madison Square Park, 26th Street, Madison Square Garden in rear (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 70, Pearl Street looking west (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 71, Pearl Street looking west to Aquarium (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 74, NY Central Freight Terminal, Riverside Drive (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 75, Trinity Place and Edgar Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 78a, Viaduct, Broadway and 125th Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 79, Wall Street, looking west, Trinity Church in distance (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 81, Whitehall and Bridge Streets, crowds watching ambulance (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 82, Whitehall Street and Pearl Street, street excavation (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 83, Whitehall and State Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 85, Whitehall Street at Pearl Street, horse-drawn truck (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 86, Horse-drawn carousel (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 87a, horse-drawn waste paper wagon on Whitehall Street at Custom House (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 88, Horse-drawn coal truck, NY Produce Exchange, 2 Broadway (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 89, Horse-drawn trucks, State Street, taken from South Ferry building (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 90, Horse-drawn emergency truck in front of Bowling Green Building, 11 Broadway, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 91, Horse-drawn dray in front of US Army Building, 39 Whitehall Street, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 92, Horse-drawn street car, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 93, Sixth Avenue "Summertime" open electric street car, 1907 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 94, Caterpillar tractor and concrete mixer in front of South Ferry Building, Whitehall Street, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 97, Snow sweeper (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 98a, US Navy Dirigible No. 254 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 98b, US Navy Dirigible No. 254 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 98c, US Navy Dirigible No. 254 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 99a, Prince Adolf of Sweden, Bowling Green, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 99b, Prince Adolf of Sweden, Bowling Green, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 99c, Prince Adolf of Sweden, Bowling Green, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 99d, Prince Adolf of Sweden, Bowling Green, 1906 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 100a, Bowling Green welcome parade, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 100b, Bowling Green welcome parade, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 100c, Bowling Green welcome parade, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 100d, Bowling Green welcome parade, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 100e, Bowling Green welcome parade, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - 101a, Parade, Bowling Green (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 101b, Parade, Bowling Green (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 102, Bowling Green, 1900 ca. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 103, Statue of George Washington, Sub Treasury Building, now Federal Hall (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 104, Statue of Henry Ward Beecher, 1923 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 105b, Statue of Ericcson, Madison Square Park, 1905 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 105a, Statue of Ericcson, Madison Square Park, winter scene, 1905 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 106, NY Harbor (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 107,Statue of Africa By Daniel Chester French, US Custom House (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 108, Daniel Webster statue, Central Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 110a, Statue of Giovanni Verrazano, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 110b, Statue of Giovanni Verrazano, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 110c, Statue of Giovanni Verrazano, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 110d, Statue of Giovanni Verrazano, Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 111, Statue of Civic Virtue, City Hall Park [moved to Queens, 1943] (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 112, Memorial Arch, Grand Army Plaza, Brooklyn (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 113, Memorial Tree to a casualty of World War I, 1918 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 115a, Washington Square Arch, double decker buses (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 115b, Washington Square Arch, horse-drawn bus (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 116a, American Merchant Marine Memorial Tablet, with flowers, 1921 after (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 116b, American Merchant Marine Memorial Tablet, 1921 after (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 117, World War I Memorial for men from the Lower East Side, by Stroughton (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 118, 59th Street Bridge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 120, Hellgate Bridge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 121, High Bridge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 122a, High Bridge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 122b, High Bridge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 122c, High Bridge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 122d, High Bridge (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 125a, Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church, 37th Street and Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 125b, Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church, 37th Street and Fifth Avenue, police on bicycle (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 125c, Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church, 37th Street and Fifth Avenue, automobiles on Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 128a, St. Patrick's Cathedral, 51st Street and Fifth Avenue (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 129, Broadway Tabernacle, 56th Street and Broadway, 1908 Oct. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 131a, Trinity Church, Broadway and Wall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 131b, Trinity Church, Broadway and Wall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 131b, Trinity Church, Broadway and Wall Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 133, Passengers on a river excursion boat, 1906 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 138, Excursion boat "Albany" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 139, Lightboat, US Engineers, "N.J. No. 1" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 140a, Coastwise freighter, "Bridgeport," New England Transportation Compa (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 140b, Coastwise freighter, "Bridgeport," New England Transportation Company (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 141, Coastwise freighter, "Mackinac" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 142, Coastwise freighter, "Priscilla" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 144, Steamship, "North Land" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 145a, US warships in Hudson River (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 145b, US warships in Hudson River (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 145c, US warships in Hudson River (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 145d, US warships in Hudson River (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 146a, Tugboat "Narragansett" (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 150, Protest meeting "Free China," Battery Park (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - 151, New York Harbor (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 152a, Municipal ferry boat, New York Harbor (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 152b, New York Harbor, Statue of Liberty in rear (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 153, New York Harbor, Battery Park, 1920 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 154a, Manhattan skyline (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 154b, Manhattan skyline with sailboat (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 155, Manhattan skyline with sailboat (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 157, Panorama, Brooklyn and Manhattan bridges (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 158, Roadside billboards (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 159, Frame house decorated with flags, 1925 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 160a, Kew Gardens Railroad Station, with commuters at train (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 161, Exchange Buffet Restaurant (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 162,Man at top of derrick (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 163a, Frank Ingalls (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 163b, Frank Ingalls (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 164f, Mr. Eddie Dorie on stilts, Broadway and Morris Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - 164g, Mr. Eddie Dorie on stilts, Broadway and Morris Street (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)